https://www.ualberta.ca/athletics/tickets/ticketing-terms-and-conditions

Terms and Conditions / Privacy Policy | Golden Bears and Pandas Athletics
Connect
Contact AthleticsAbout UsChampionship TraditionDigital MediaSocial Media - @BearsandPandasAthletics/GGSS WebinarFan Code of ConductMaster of CoachingVisiting TeamsGreen & Gold Sport SystemFan GuideJob Opportunities & InternshipsMerchandiseVolunteerVarsity Health
Teams
Golden Bears BasketballPandas BasketballGolden Bears FootballPandas RugbyGolden Bears HockeyPandas HockeyGolden Bears SoccerPandas SoccerGolden Bears VolleyballPandas VolleyballCross-countryCurlingSwimmingTennisTrack and FieldWrestling
Alumni
Sports Wall of FameChuck Moser Celebration of LifeUpdate Your Contact InformationAlumni News ArchiveBlock AClare Drake's LegacyGreen and Gold Athletic SocietyGreen and Gold Athletic Society Alumni AwardsAlumni Merchandise
Giving
Bears and Pandas OpenFundraising GoalsSupport The SportWestJet & Delta Air Lines RaffleWomen Fore Pandas Golf TournamentScholarships and AwardsGreen & Gold Honey LagerUAlberta Donor Impact Report
Schedules
Complete Scores and SchedulesAlberta Cup
Tickets
NEW - Digital TicketingOnline SalesSeason TicketsIndividual Ticket PricingKids in the CrowdUAlberta Student Access2020 U SPORTS Track & Field ChampionshipEvent Pass RegistrationBears Den & Saville Suites RentalsDonate Tickets to KidsBag PolicyTerms and Conditions / Privacy PolicyVenue Seating Maps
Home
Tickets
Terms and Conditions / Privacy Policy
Terms and Conditions / Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy – Account Manager – June 28, 2019 (Updated Sept 9, 2019)
The Golden Bears & Pandas’ Account Manager, located at https://am.ticketmaster.com/universityofalberta/#/ and https://am.ticketmaster.com/uofastudent/#/, is provided, owned and/or operated by the University of Alberta.
This page states the Personal Information and Privacy Policy by which Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics and users of the Website abide (“Privacy Policy”). This Privacy Policy applies if you access the Website through any device, including without limitation a smart phone, smart TV, tablet, laptop or desktop computer, or through any other means. This privacy Policy applies only to information collected through the Website and does not apply to information collected offline by Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics. Athletics has created and implemented this Privacy Policy so that you understand how your personal information may be collected, retained, used, disclosed, and destroyed and how it is protected by Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics.
By providing personal information while using the Website and dealing with Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics, you consent to the collection, retention, use, disclosure, destruction and protection of your personal information in accordance with the terms set out in this Privacy Policy.
Should you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please contact Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics using the contact information provided at the end of this Privacy Policy.
Compliance with legislation
Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics complies with the Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy (FOIP) Act, and Canada’s Anti-Spam Legislation (CASL), which are designed to protect your personal information and privacy.
Protection of Privacy - The personal information requested on this form is collected under the authority of Section 33 (c) of the Alberta Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act and will be protected under Part 2 of that Act. It will be used for the purpose of administering student, alumni, and supporter relations at the University of Alberta and providing advanced services and information on products, events, and services that may be of interest to you.  This will include order and payment processing, customer service and quality assurance, as well as contacting you for offers and promotions. Please note that information collected will be transmitted to and stored on servers outside of the University, Alberta and Canada and that the University cannot guarantee protection against disclosures as a consequence of foreign laws.  Direct any questions about this collection to:  Athletics Ticketing Associate, University of Alberta, 4-414 Van Vliet Complex, Edmonton Alberta, T6G 2H9, 780-492-9441.  Please also see the University of Alberta’s privacy statement.
Our Commitment to Your Privacy
Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics is committed to protecting your personal information and privacy and considers matters relating to the protection of your personal information and privacy to be of the utmost importance. Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics adheres to the following principles to protect your privacy:
Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics does not sell, rent, loan, trade, lease, transfer or otherwise disclose your personal information to third parties
All information which you provide to Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics will be protected with industry-stand protocols and technology
Definitions
Unless otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, the terms used herein shall be defined as in the FOIP Act, where applicable. In this Privacy Policy the following terms has the following meaning:
“Personal Information” means the recorded information about an identifiable individual, including, but not limited to:
The individual’s name, home or business address, or home or business telephone number;
the individual’s age, sex, marital status or family status;
information about the individual’s educational history
the individual’s personal views or opinions, except if they are about someone else
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a new privacy policy on the Website in place of this one. The date on which the Privacy Policy was last amended is indicated at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. The amended Privacy Policy shall automatically be effective when posted and will apply to information collected after the effective date. Amendments may include, without limitation, additions, deletions or modifications to this Privacy Policy.
Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics will post notice that the Privacy Policy has been amended on the fronting webpage of the Website located at am.ticketmaster.com/universityofalberta for a period of 30 days. You are advised to check for such notices and to review the Privacy Policy each time you use the Website in order to ensure that you are aware of any amendments and that they are acceptable to you.
Your continued use of the Website following the posting of an amended Privacy Policy and the related notice means that you accept the terms of this Privacy Policy as amended. If you do not agree with any of the terms or conditions in the amended Privacy Policy, then you agree to immediately cease all use of the Website, which shall be your sole recourse and remedy in the event your are dissatisfied with the amended Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy may not otherwise be amended.
Personal Information Aggregated or Made Anonymous
To the extent that Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics makes any of your personal information anonymous or aggregates it with the personal information of others such that it can no longer be attributed to you, your information will no longer be considered to be personal information and Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics is entitled to use, retain, disclose and destroy such information in its absolute discretion.
Choosing to Provide Personal Information
When using the Website and dealing with Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics, you may choose not to provide certain aspects of your personal information. If you choose not to provide all information reasonably requested of you, it may limit the manner in which you can make use of the Website and otherwise interact with Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics or you may not be able to use the Website or to interact with Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics at all.
Consent
By using the Website, you provide implied consent to the collection, retention, use, disclosure, destruction and protection of your personal information by Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Your implied consent may be obtained through amendments to this Privacy Policy, as provided above.
Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics will obtain your express consent prior to or when collecting, using or disclosing your personal information in cases of sensitive information, for a purpose that is not described in this Privacy Policy, or for a purpose that Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics did not identify to you or that was not reasonably expected at the time of collection, unless Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics is required or authorized by law not to obtain your consent.
You provide implied consent to the collection, retention, use, and disclosure of your personal information for a particular purpose if you voluntarily provide the information to Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics for that particular purpose and it is reasonable that a person would voluntarily provide that information.
In certain circumstances, including without limitation when dealing with certain legal, medical or security issues, Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics may be authorised or required by law to disclose your personal information without seeking or obtaining your knowledge or consent.
Consent via Opt-In or Opt-Out in Certain Circumstances
Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics may, from time to time, provide you with a reasonable opportunity to opt-out of certain collections, uses and disclosures of your personal information. You implicitly consent to a particular collection use or disclosure of your personal information if you fail to indicate within a reasonable time that you wish to opt-out of the particular collection, use or disclosure when you are given a reasonable opportunity to do so.
Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics may, from time to time, provide you with a reasonable opportunity to opt-in to certain collections, uses and disclosures of your personal information. If you do not opt-in to a particular collection, use or disclosure of your personal information when given a reasonable opportunity to do so, you do not consent to your personal information being collected, used or disclosed in that particular manner.
Where Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics provides an opt-in or opt-out opportunity, Athletics will use the opt-out method when particular collection, use or disclosure does not pertain to sensitive information or would be reasonably expected by the user of the Website. Athletics will use the opt-in method in all other circumstances.
Changing or Withdrawing Consent
You may change or withdraw your consent with respect to the collection, retention, use, disclosure, destruction and protection of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy at any time, subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice, by contacting Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics using the contact information provided at the end of this Privacy Policy and by providing Athletics with sufficient personal identifiers so that it can act effectively on your request.
Collection of Personal Information
Personal information about you that Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics collects will be collected directly from you by Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics. Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics will obtain your consent to collect your personal information and will inform you at that time of the uses and disclosures that Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics intends to make of your personal information, unless the intended uses and disclosures are described in the Privacy Policy or are reasonably expected at the time that Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics collects your personal information.
The following, without limitation, are particular circumstances in which Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics may collect your personal information:
When you register an account through Account Manager, subscribe to Be The Roar Newsletter, subscribe to Scores Weekly, purchase tickets through Account Manager or Ticketmaster.ca, respond to an electronic survey or communication from Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics.
Golden Bears & Pandas athletics also may collect information, including without limitation, the name, address, email address of recipients of ticket transfers. Such information about the recipient would be provided by the individual accepting the transfer.
Use of Personal Information
When Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics uses your personal information, it will ensure that you previously provided consent to the intended use or it will obtain your consent prior to using your personal information in that particular manner, unless the intended use is described in this Privacy Policy, was identified to you or was reasonably expected at the time that Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics collected your personal information, or is permitted or required by law without your consent.
The following, without limitation, are particular circumstances in which Golden Bears & Pandas may use your personal information without obtaining further consent. By providing your personal information you consent to the following uses:
Using identification and contact information, such as your name, address and e-mail address, to provide you with information about Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics when you request that information
Using identification and contact information, such as your name, address and e-mail address, so that Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics can identify you and deliver the products, services, promotions, newsletters, that you request and can communicate with you regarding those products, services, promotions and newsletters including without limitation when responding to your customer service requests
Using payment method preferences and related financial information that you provide to Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics so that Athletics can obtain payment for the products and services that you request and can process transactions in an efficient manner
Using customer relationship information such as your products and service requests, instructions, comments and feedback to assist Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics in delivering products and services and the Website in accordance with your preferences
Using your email address to administer a promotion or survey or to provide you with information about events that may interest you or new features and/or enhancements to Golden Bears & Pandas products and services and to the Website, unless you choose to unsubscribe to such messages in accordance with CASL, where applicable
Using identification information and contact information, such as your name, address and email address to send you promotional material or special offers on our behalf of our marketing partners and/or their respective affiliates and subsidiaries and other third parties
Analyzing your personal information to assist Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics in developing and enhancing its products and services or the Website
Analyzingyour personal information to assist Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics in conducting market analysis and strategic planning
Links to Other Websites
The Website may contain links to other websites or online services that are operated and maintained by third parties and that are not under our control or maintained by us. Such links do not constitute an endorsement by use of those other websites, the content displayed therein, or the person or entities associated therewith. This Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party content.
Security of Personal Information
Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics recognizes its obligation to protect personal information that is in its custody or under its control by implementing reasonable security safeguards to keep confidential and secure you your personal information against risks such as loss, theft, and unauthorized access, collection, use, disclosure, copying, modification, disposal or destruction. The reasonable safeguards may vary depending on the circumstances, including the level of sensitivity of the personal information, and may include secured networks, restricting access to authorized individuals on a need-to-know basis, locked door, other organizational, physical or technological security measures, and contractual measures such as non-disclosure or confidentiality agreements.
Children’s Privacy Policy – Users under 13 Years Old (“Children”)
Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics does not knowingly collect Personal Information from Children, except for possibly collecting the name of the child during the purchase of a youth season ticket package by a parent or guardian. Children are not permitted to submit Personal Information via the website for the purposes of, but not limited to, any current or future promotions.
Should you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics Account Manager Privacy Policy, practices, or handling of your personal information or if you wish to request access to or correction of your personal information under Golden Bears & Pandas care and control, you may contact Golden Bears & Pandas Athletics at:
Address: Faculty of Kinesiology, Sport, and Recreation
2-420 Van Vliet Complex
Edmonton AB, Canada T6G 2H9
Phone: 780-492-9441
Email: gameday@ualberta.ca
Golden Bears and Pandas Athletics
Tickets
Faculty of Kinesiology, Sport, and Recreation
University of Alberta 116 St. and 85 Ave., Edmonton, AB, Canada T6G 2R3 · We are located on Treaty 6 / Métis Territory.
